CURRICULUM VITAE

PERSONAL DATA:

Name: JOHN KAISER

E-mail: johnkaiser964@gmail.com

Phone: +254795655023

Portfolio: https://johnkaizer.github.io/

SUMMARY (PROFILE/PROJECTS):

I am an android developer, using Android studio and frameworks like flutter to develop android applications that meet user's needs and requirements. I have experience in developing android applications using both Java (2+ years) and Kotlin (1+years). I have been able to develop several applications using the two languages.

While working at Tech and Beyond, I developed and managed an application that helped in monitoring the transactions and other activities in a weighbridge station.

In my time at Flair Edge, I have developed sustainable software that meets user's requirements and needs. I worked on a system to digitize the process of locating house units to rent, fumigators and cleaners dubbed SmartHama.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY:

01.2021- To Date FLAIR EDGE, SOFTWARE ENGINEER

- Developing and maintaining web Applications that are sustainable.
- Performed maintenance on developed application.

12.2021- 12.2022 TECH AND BEYOND, ANDROID DEVELOPER

- Developed and managed android application for monitoring weighbridge station transactions and other activities.
- Performed maintenance on developed application.

07.2021- 09.2021 TRACOM SERVICES LIMITED, POS DEVELOPER INTERN

- Conducting tests and performance reviews on already developed applications.
- Writing code

EDUCATION:

2019 – 2022	KCA UNIVERSITY Bachelor of Science Degree in Information Technology
2015 – 2018	MUSINGU BOYS HIGH SCHOOL Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education

TRAINING:

06.2022 – 12.2022 GOOGLE AFRICA DEVELOPERS SCHOLARSHIPS

Android Developer Track

Associates Developers Certification

03.2021-06.2021 TRACOM SERVICES LIMITED ACADEMY

Fullstack Developer Training

Certification

SKILLS PROFILE:

- ✓ Skills:
 - Java, Kotlin ,JavScript
 - Spring boot, ReactJs and NodeJs
 - Git (GitHub and Bitbucket)
 - MySQL, MongoDb and SQlite
 - Team work and communication skills
- ✓ Languages:
 - English
 - Swahili
- ✓ Certificates:
 - Udacity nano-degree courses on android development.
 - Associates Android Developer

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION:

- ✓ Hobbies:
 - Playing field hockey
 - Listening to music

REFFEREES:

- 1. IGNATIOUS OJIAMBO +254706151591
 - ignatiusojiambo@gmail.com
- 2. FAUSTINE KHASEYI
 - +25479360057

faustinekhaseyi@gmail.com